<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Systematic Review and Metaanalysis of Unconditional Cash Transfer Studies</title>
      <link>/services/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/meta/</guid>
      <description>Since May 2020, EPL members have systematically searched, collected, categorized, and analyzed the recent but vast literature analyzing the effects of unconditional cash transfers (UCTs) on household welfare.
At present, students are empirically analyzing the characteristics of these studies and their findings in order to draw more general inferences on the state of the literature and the types of programs that have been studied.
This project will result in a full-length manuscript to be submitted to an academic journal by Spring 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Aid Effects on Women and Children</title>
      <link>/services/eval/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/eval/</guid>
      <description>This project looks to estimate the effects of humanitarian aid programs on women and children in recipient refugee households in Lebanon.
Project lead: Hassan Kenawi
Contributors: Jackson Schneider, Nicholas Skelley, Will Wanner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raoul Dubey</title>
      <link>/team/raoul-dubey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/raoul-dubey/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Raoul Dubey and I&amp;rsquo;m a Junior majoring in Economics and Mathematics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poverty Targeting Model</title>
      <link>/services/targeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/targeting/</guid>
      <description>This project aims to develop a machine-learning based poverty targeting model for refugees in Kenya&amp;rsquo;s Kalobeyei Settlement.
Project lead: Colleen O&amp;rsquo;Donnell
Contributors: Carlos Guzman, Alec Russin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emlyn Langlieb</title>
      <link>/team/emlyn-langlieb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/emlyn-langlieb/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Emlyn. I am majoring in Economics and minoring in Sociology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karoline Lin</title>
      <link>/team/karoline-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/karoline-lin/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Karoline and I am a senior at Emory University majoring in Quantitative Sciences and Economics. I am passionate about data science because it allows me to bridge my economics foundation with my analytical skills. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to apply what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned in the past few years in the Emory Policy Lab. Outside of work, you can find me playing volleyball, making glass art or travelling. Fun fact: I&amp;rsquo;ve traveled to 10 countries in the past 3 years!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sirui Hu</title>
      <link>/team/sirui-hu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/sirui-hu/</guid>
      <description>Add information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us</title>
      <link>/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/apply/</guid>
      <description>Students wishing to become involved in EPL are expected to prepare and meet the following requirements:
 Have taken ECON 220 and 320 (or equivalent) and demonstrate beyond-classroom experience or interest in quantitative skills using either R, Python, or another object-oriented language. Have a Github account and are able to perform basic Git functions and processes (push/pull/merge) to work collaboratively Be willing to actively collaborate on a daily or every-other-day basis via Slack with a project team Be familiar with LaTeX and/or Overleaf Have prepared a simple professional website  We accept students as rising Sophomores through to Seniors; to join, send an e-mail to the director with a one page description of your preparation and interest in joining the EPL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
